

younes.khoubaz@gmail.com

younes.khouba

★ Zone d'Activité, 50 Saknia

math Date of birth 06/08/2002

% younes-khoubaz.netlify.app

Moroccan

♥ Kénitra

+212 687 749447

Single 3

${f A}$ Languages

English

Advanced

French

Advanced

German

■ B1

Arabic

Fluent



Soft Skills

Collaboration

Time Management

Fast learning

Reliabality



Interests

Cosmology

Open-World Games

Alternative Rock Music

Summary

I am a highly motivated Full Stack Developer with a bachelor's degree specializing in computer science and information technology. I have experience working on diverse software projects including administrative apps as well as user-oriented platforms. Skilled in .NET and ReactJS.

Education

From 2023 to 2024

Bachelor's in mathematics and computer science

University of Ibn-Tofail Kenitra, Morocco

From 2020 to 2022

University diploma of technology (DUT)

Ecole Supérieur de Technologie Kenitra, Morocco

Computer engineering

2020 Baccalaureate

Al Majd Al Assil Kenitra, Morocco

- Physics and chemistry sciences
- Excellency

Experience

From April 2024 to June 2024 Designed and developed an online courses platform

Faculty of Science, Ibn-Tofail University / Kénitra

Designed to streamline the learning process for students through simplified lessons and intuitive interface

enhancing their educational experience

From October 2023 to March 2024 Created a business travel validation system

CITIC Dicastal /Kénitra (Free Zone)

Reduced the approval process time, made handling requests much easier and fast, eliminated paper usage to help save the environment, and enabled data tracking.

From April 2022 to June 2022

Developed a graduation thesis management platform

Ecole Supérieur de Technologie / Kénitra

Significantly improved organsing graduation theses for the administration and simplified various tasks for students

and teachers.

From April 2022 to June 2022 Implemented a resource management system

The Court of Appeals / Kénitra

Optimized equipment distribution by tracking stock, introduced employee tracking between workplaces, and an archive functionality to enhance workflow efficiency.

Technical Skills

Programming languages, Frameworks & Tools

- C#, Java, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, T-SQL
- .NET Web API, ReactJS, Redux, Redux-Saga
- Git, Azure Cloud, Docker
- UML, Merise